Give it up evening for Shastri Singh.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
I'm in my mid 30s currently. I turn
35 recently. Ah then I turned 36 also. Ah
I have a little problem. Ok. I have my
There is always some hesitation in revealing one's age.
In fact, there is so much hesitation that every time
I have asked this question before
Process the question from my mouth
The smaller number is automatically selected.
And I Never Thought It's a Big Deal I Think
Okay brother, what can I do now?
Am. But recently I have been informed
Okay, by one of my younger friends, of course.
This is apparently very problematic behavior.
Is. Apparently, I'm doing this because
Because somewhere deep inside my subconscious
Believes that in aging women
There is no value in the society. are understanding
You guys? So my subconscious keeps me in the game
To keep alive. automatically minus one
and is outputting it.
I felt very embarrassed after hearing this. What happened?
[ __ ] man, how stupid I turned out to be.
subconscious
How much of a fool did you become once?
I am able to subtract only one number
[Appreciation]
I have studied so much maths and science in my life.
I don't have the confidence to make it minus five.
I can come [laughs]
My age is 37 actually ok but I need a
minute to get comfortable ok now i am done
Comfortable like actually came also till 2018
I used to have a corporate job, okay?
Used to have a job in marketing and
Stand Up Used to Be My Hobby 2018
Since then, stand-up has become my job and
Therapy Has Become My Hobby
I'm really into therapy, actually a little bit.
Passion is the same type, let me tell you yes
I'm one of those people I see as a therapist
When I go near you, I just bring questions.
Complete research analysis by forming a team
I go, I will tell him too, someone
Good conversation of travelling na a in
My In My Early Days in Therapy My Questions
He was a bit of a youthful type, okay I would
Present to her problems like that you know
what that I you know I understand
that the men I like, they don't
Typically like me back and because otherwise
I'm so perfect I think this
is happening because I am attracted to
emotionally unavailable men because I have some
There is a mental health issue. Yes. so can you help
Me decode that figure that out. those early days
My therapist just told me
It was that look at the people who have mental health issues
It happens that he comes to therapy jumping around so much.
Not there.
They are not that excited about us.
I had to push them to get close.
Is. I am saying that your enthusiasm is therapy.
I would not worry too much after seeing him
About your mental health. saying most
What is probably happening is that that man
Just Don't Like You OK
Which is okay, which is all right you have to
Like you people don't have to like you okay of
Of course it was quite bootle, this conversation on butt
Once I digested this, it was
Easy for me to move on in life over years
I would like to believe that my questions to him
It had become a little deeper at some point
I was telling my therapist that I understood
I have come to know that attachment is also a problem for every person.
is the root of. Yes, I understand. Very
I have watched YouTube videos on this topic.
Pay. Yes, I understand. I want to
If I do love etc. now then I will become a Sufi
I should do something woofy type. Yes, Khwaja is
I should operate in my Khwaja zone. Yes
That my love is so true and so abundant
yes. Yes, that love itself should be its reward
In itself. I say I love you and run away
I will take it. Are? And I have such a thought in my mind
Let the feeling happen. Ok.
I am asking him that when I take so much
If I am loving truly and abundantly then
Why do I feel so disconnected again?
Is?
Can you help me solve that? When I do all this
I was just talking, then I could see bold in
My Therapist Eyes. ok yes on his face
There was such a death look. Yes, he is mine
I waited patiently for him to finish the whole conversation.
And then suddenly she says, look, I can
Summarize your problem for you in two lines.
Say, your problem is that you
Looks like you are very evolved. We you
You seem very innovative and genuine.
You are walking a very basic bed.
The sooner we get to know this
The sooner we get on the path to healing
You can move ahead. And she's telling you more
There is no problem. some other problem
No. All you need is a lonely dying inside you
There is fear. which is very normal ok
Which is part of the human condition. saying
Yours truly, Extra Pathetic
Extra [ __ ] compulsive is extra needy.
But it is solvable. Ok? And I Feel Again
This conversation was very insulting, but
Very insightful. ah because with as you do you
No Ways to Overcome Your Fear of Dying
Alone, right? With age, you know, you start
Liking Your Own Company, With As You Start
Hating Other People's Company. Ah With Age
Realize how good a format friendship is
Is. Do not be alone. If your friend is married
If yes, they will help you a lot. because you hang
Out with your married friends. Your Fear of
Dying loan is completely eliminated.
Like brother, death goes by very quickly.
Has been. What is this long horror story going on?
It is with these people.
The Grass Has Never Been Less Been on the Other
Side. What are we doing with the grass?
People?
with as you also realize that you know life
I will definitely feel happy. you on your bus
What is in me is your perspective.
Perspective Start Figuring Out How To
Improve your perspective on life. So I
For this, many philosophers have to
I follow you on Instagram.
[nasal sound]
Very helpful okay. One One Buddhist Monk
I follow him and keep repeating that you know a good
The Way to Exist in the World Is Where You Are
Feel I am okay and you are okay. Oh, this I
I practiced for a few years and realized this
Only Buddhist monks can say everything.
Are. who himself climbs the mountain and sits there
and are not interacting with the world at all
There are. Everyone here is saying that
Looks cute.
It looks very cute. very beautiful
It's enough. Don't come near and irritate me
Times.
I think that's for most of us regulars.
Ficus religiosa. A More Practical Way to Exist In
The World Is Where You Feel I'm Not Okay.
But you are verse.
I am not okay.
[Appreciation]
I am not okay but you are so bad. I feel better.
Ok?
No matter how much I have lost you in my life
It looks a bit too cut off. what a
Beautiful Way to Exist. Ok. I think
This is how we all operate by default.
That our child has failed in school.
Oh [ __ ] but he's doing drugs.
Our daughter-in-law talks using abusive language. his
She hits me with her slippers. Oh my god
There is so much emptiness in my life. Loneliness
Is. Oh no they have two kids. Oh my God
then sit
Our Modi ji is his drum. Oh my god
Please sit so much.
Shameless
Shameless.
Say look at yourself okay. I think
In the last two and a half years, we
The happiness index automatically went up.
Went.
People are saying brother, we should get it cut.
Get it cut, look people, what are you getting yours done?
with? Is there vote theft going on there? What
Was it his compulsion brother?
What I'm telling you is you know I think
many of us know now that you know that your
Mental health is going well. One of its
The sign is that brother, on his worst day
You should also not feel jealous of someone else.
You just assume that brother, we are sad.
So what? Ambani also feels sad sometimes.
It must be friend. There are problems in everyone's life
remains. It's a Very Healthy Way to
Exist. But the opposite also happens that you
No, sometimes you realize that your mental state is so
It's going badly that no matter how much you support someone
Listen to my sorrow, do you think he has just said this to me?
He has not opened his mouth. When my story
Will you come out? even the birds cry
I will give it brother. Are? tears of the universe
Will go. [Laughter]
okay so last year some time if we last
Year I found myself in this state that where
I am talking to someone and if
What is the biggest problem going on in your life?
Yes, if you tell me about it, I will pity myself
I'll start eating upstairs, okay, I will.
Explain I will explain like one day
I was talking to my college friend.
I have a college friend who now lives in London.
I work for Facebook
Call her just to say happy birthday
Did it go on its own tangent?
She said, what a birthday, what a birthday, so many
We have grown up, do you know how much?
I have a job and two children.
The dog is also a husband.
I deal with all this throughout the day. Then I
Attendance on the mums' WhatsApp group
I am going to apply it. Then I take the husband to his four
I will remind you of the work. Then I bottles
I sell it. Then I sleep. Then
I wake up and the same day repeats itself.
It happens. And she says this is the worst part
That I collected everything by myself
Is. Yes, I ticked all these boxes myself.
I want this in my life, this too
I want it, I want this too, now I have it all. I
Hate it all. I'm in the Prison of My Own
Creation. I can't even run away, I don't know
what to do full ok
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Full rank happening and I'm saying what
She is a most ungrateful woman, yes she has given me so much.
That is why God has given him so many challenges.
Isn't it so, look at me, I'm still sitting
I keep counting likes on Instagram
Tell me, my life is going so sad.
This time I didn't think much about it.
About two or three months after this, I
The other one went to meet a friend. This one which
she is my friend
Environmentalist.
She Got Her Degree in Her Masters and
Climate Change from Scotland
University of Edinburgh. and then your heart
For goodness sake, I came back to India to fix it.
The Climate of New Delhi. Ok.
Then he was suffering from depression for the last 5 years.
Are. Continuous Ok. I think to give her
Credit. I feel people like her. Yes, my
Friends who go into social work
or go to work on the environmental side
He is actually very pure at heart.
There are soft people who truly feel
that their actions will change the world
and then they are cut off
Of course ok I have seen her said many
times but last year when I was meeting
Her I Could See She Is Having a Mental
Breakdown ok sitting in front of me literally
She was crying and saying she didn't know.
That's how to moisten yourself
Literally every image of others' pens
Pain Anywhere Brings Me Pain It Feels Like
A personal loss, there's a flood somewhere, somewhere
There is a drought, somewhere there is a war going on.
So many people are dying. I don't know how to
Deal with this. I do feel so helpless. This
What is the benefit of education? When I do something
I am not able to. any government in the world
It is not serious anywhere. no one does anything
Used to be. The future is so bleak, so
Depressing. I feel so sad. Full Rand
Happening. And I am saying this clearly
There is no problem in personal life.
Its.
Tears are being shed directly on global matters.
What a luxury to have.
Yes, love life, job, everything must be going great.
Brother.
Look at me, my heart is hurting
Have kept it. Yes, I can't find the bandwidth.
There is something else to think about. ok why she is
Howling in Front of Me. In That Moment
A voice came into my mind, "Brother,
Time to pay the therapist back.
Already happened. Something seems off
In your mind. So I Went Back To
My therapist. Ok. I said hello! So
I am back. I said look, don't be afraid
It doesn't matter to you. This time I am some
I have not come with any basic [ __ ] type issue. This
This time I have become something big. Some?
So a deeper existential crisis type of thing.
It has arrived. Some abstract sadness overwhelms me
I am feeling it. And I see the therapist
She said, look, I have been watching for many years.
You don't seem impressed with me at all.
Have been. I am constantly trying.
I am completely lost in this silent love for your face.
I am just looking at the sentiments. I said
So this time I will not share my trauma points
I have made a PPT of this and brought it. Yes I
I have made a list and brought it. Yes, that we
You can start from here and you can also see brother
Bad things have happened to me. So I him
Nor am I reading out my PPT.
I said, first of all, of course, when I pass 12th
After that I did not get into IIT. So yes that
My whole life in the shadow of rejection
It has gone out. Secondary of Course in College
My first breakup after was also very next
Was. I did all the next incidents but
Next time, yes, he would leave me alone with the guilt.
Not there. And then I'm saying I was in
My Early 20s Also When My Father Passed
Away It Was Quite Sudden For Us. I am not
Sure if we process it properly. And
I stopped here and I said, this is
It is solid, isn't it? Are? You can do a little on this
Tell me something.
My therapist took a deep breath. Ok. look
At me. She's like, I'm sorry about this thing.
Happened to you. These are, of course, very sad
Events. But then she said she liked but this
Things Happen to You in Your Fair Adulthood
which means by that time you were already
Fairly Cooked | Ah
[Laughter]
Means
She See Cooked Vegetables Don't Get Spoiled
That's Easy | It Is The Fresh Produce That
Is more vulnerable?
[Laughter]
You guys don't have a one semester metaphor.
What is it?
[Appreciation]
We only have one hour of time, right?
So what do you want? how many times means
Said inside him every time reference spread
You people cannot elaborate on the explanation.
I said, tell me straight away what to say.
Do you want to? Unfortunately for my
Comedy My Therapist Always Makes Sense In
The End. So What She Explained to Me
which is actually something many of you
Already know how most of us are deeper
Existential Issues Are Attachment Problems
Our insecurities are all part of our adulthood.
I see it but it takes a little time to make it.
Formed Way Earlier Than My Therapist Told
I think most of these issues originate literally
When you are a baby in your infancy
Depending on how your primary caregiver is
Which is typically how our mother handled you.
Basically, your mother held you in her lap.
Based on how much clumsy you picked up
The entire personality may turn out to be cringe.
I said, brother, now tell this to my mother.
Don't tell.
OK to be late. ok already i blame
Her for Everything Else. yes that's my hair
Jhave, it is because of you. my jaw
Panche, this is because of you. Now I will tell them
that the rest of the rituals are proactively
That all is your responsibility too
Not done ok guys you must know of course I
Have no memory. I have little recollection of that
How My Mother Handled Me When I Was a
Child. But I know two things. The Fact
Number One Is Mother Was Only 23 When She Had
Me. Ok? And I've been 23, I know 23.
Ok? The Truth About 23 Is You're Just 23
And the Truth About Motherhood Is and Motherhood
It is hard. Ok? It probably is the most
The Super Human Thing You Can Do in This One
Life. It is hard. Ok? So my assumption
Is that at the age of 23, no matter how much you have inside
Enthusiasm that wow, it will be fun to become a mom
Will go. The joy of becoming a mother. Oh my God. How much
It may also have been your own decision. Ok. 23
When This Reality Hits
You. Ok. When your four-month-old baby starts to sleep
Not giving consistently. When the child you
using a vending machine type and a
I am not putting a 25 paise coin inside you by mistake.
[Appreciation] I think it's a fair assumption
That your 23 year old brain did not say anything.
Wow, life has become so much fun. this is the
Best life ever. most likely once in
A while your secret thought was that oh my god
This is very very hard. The rest of the moms
How did you underplay this thing so much? Me
Why are bravery awards not being given every day?
To do? This child's face is my breath
Why are you going to pay?
100%
100% happening ok
On top of this when it comes to handling.
[sound of clearing throat] Okay? I know that
My mom, okay, my mom, to that generation
She belongs. Ok? the roles of women who
Model the women like Rani Lakshmibai in
Mother India. Do you guys understand? that the children
in one hand [laughs] and with the other
Go out to plough.
Brother, there should be double income in the house. child's
How will we secure the future? For them
There is no idea that the child should wiggle around.
I have been insecure all my life.
I'm telling my therapist. This is this
It's really tragic. The therapist is saying
Dude, tragic for you, very good for me
Business. Ok. Then the whole bandra sat here
It has happened all day long.
So I told him okay, okay, that
Explain this, explain something because
my my people pleasing issues, my
Anxiety, This Explains. I said then
But what I get is abstract void
I feel this big pen coming to me
He's come in, I don't think I need him.
The answer is being found in this conversation, so we
Can we explore a little more? Say
Explore as much as you can afford.
Will take. Brother Oh, that's our job.
No, we are sitting here too, so we are
Exploring Further OK We're Looking Back
At my childhood we are taking a trip
Down the memory line to see whose challan
Where to cut, very good exercise.
The next thing I realized was when I
was very small my role model was my father
I was very clear that I too would grow up
I have to become a man like my father. I was like
Wow what a life. Ok. Yes, I was like,
Wow! between father and mother but father's
The jackpot is gone. I was very
I just want to become a father when the day grows older.
Then find a mummy type character.
I will come for my life. [Laughter]
Mummy came and managed my entire life from A to Z.
I will do it. I take my tiffin to the office in the morning.
I will go. Yes, I will come back from office and then watch TV.
I will see.
I would like to have a more balanced life than this
I can't do it. I am beyond this
Nothing more is needed than this. That's all I need
Needed And I was always confused
Other little girls get these brain waves.
Why can't you find it? Yes, all these people
Why move towards the Optimal Life Path?
Are? I tell you it's the kind of feeling no
Which sometimes comes to you at the airport. When
You go to the airport, you get a ticket on one side.
A very long line is visible and on one side there is a
A very small line is visible. Like all these
Why are you donkeys standing in this long line, friend?
Can't they see this small line?
Yes. And then you go to a short line like,
Oh! What DG travel? oh sorry sorry sorry
Sorry.
Is that feeling? [Appreciation]
so basically
By the time [sound of clearing throat] came
Become a teenager ok oops I don't have DG
Travel OK
O it is possible for me to become a man in this life
Man will not be able to stand in the line of people
Already too much man
Men are unable to become men themselves.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation] Society's Major Pain Point Chal
Used to be. People are doing research on this.
I said brother, the shoe will go that way.
I will eat it only.
So as a teenager I realized for the first time
Time that oh the best possible option available
To me it is I became a high achieving woman.
Ok? I Became the Kind of Woman Who Hard Work
By doing this she acquires everything that someone
A man can get it in this life. So
May you sleep well in life
The moon can definitely become your life. Ok?
Yes. I realise it is possible. But now I
I also realized that if I had to go this way
So I also need a female role model. My
Father cannot be the ideal role model. because
I think as we grow up we also realize
That life is not just life. Life
There is a race and the purpose of life is to win this race
In we have to get to the forefront of the part. But
You also realize that in this race if a man
People are running on foot, so we ladies
The sack has been tied. Yes, we have such
I have to run away. Yes, a little bit of us
Constraint diff is running. So dad
How will you practice it? Yes, I came
Need a Sack Race Champion Now.
So first I looked towards my mother.
Yes. I said that even mommy has less qualities.
Not there. It's not like that. working woman
Managing the Household Kind Person Good
Sense of humor. And I said this woman who
She is so worried. On their efforts
The returns are coming so week. yes this to me
The lifestyle doesn't seem fun. So I
Gave the brief to mom only. I said mommy
Listen to No Hard Feelings. Yes, Consolation
Wise. [Laughter]
And I'm saying you understand. ok you
I understand that now that I am a scout
If I am living then I want something superlative.
Ok? I want to find a woman who
You have achieved so much in life.
You have achieved so much that seeing
Other women should feel like doing this too.
It was possible. What thank you for doing this.
We had no idea. Thank you for opening
That door. That much. And I am telling that the
The kind of woman who achieved so much
Maybe after seeing this people will say that this
How are you?
[Laughter]
Did her husband do her homework?
Did he have any scenes with the boss here? It's Not In
These words. Okay, but I'm telling my mother
Can you find someone? Mummy is saying that
We have a woman in mind for you. Say
She is your distant aunt
Are. At this point she also knows that we
This is the culture that our villages and neighborhoods
If any person in the building is an IAS
If he becomes an officer then we will see our family tree.
People just extend it and take it to that point.
We would have wrapped them in our relationship.
Are.
to this dead I am not clear how this sudo
Aunt of mine. Exactly my aunt. Mummy
She is saying that the question is not relevant at all.
I have given my consent, you go ahead. But
[Laughter]
But his story is definitely very
Inspiring. Ok? I was told some 60-
70 Years Ago This Woman Grew Up in a Very
Small village near Ballia. where to study
There was no culture of it. literally became the
First girl ever to get educated there.
scholarship, he completed his degree etc.
Completed it. After that I cleared UPSC.
Become an IAS officer, not just any kind
Who really makes a difference. work on education
Did it, reduced corruption. And to do all this
After One Day She Got Board of It. She Likes Now
I have to earn money. So So She Quit All Of
Dec. He has his own one
started an investment fund and then in it
While working, she has become so big now that
Now all the rich people want to become richer than him.
Let's take advice. She Is a Kind of a
Persons who come to the news to gain knowledge that
Brother, where should I invest the money? His Malabar
There is a three-storey house in the Hills. I said
Wow what a story. what a story same
This woman at birth embraced feminism, nationalism,
Capitalism did everything. And just keep pushing
It is happening brother. [Commendation] without a gold medal
It is not coming back from anywhere. I I
Was 16 at this point, okay, I had never
Met every. Done. She was in Mumbai. I that
The time was in Lucknow. But just the idea of ​​her
Was Enough For Me. Every day I woke up in the morning and
Think about her and it would motivate me so
Much to work hard. For a whole year I
He must have been worshipped like a god. And one day
Mom is saying today is your lucky day.
Today that aunt is coming home to meet you.
Go and get ready. I go and powder and
It fell into the oil cans. Brother.
I said, brother, have you ever been so prepared?
Not for anyone.
[sound of clearing throat]
In the evening she came to our house and she was
Everything I Had Imagined Her to Be. some people
They walk into a room. You can see that
They have some different star quality going on.
Is. His aura is different. She was one of two
Ficus religiosa. And I think people like her who are so
Accomplished. He doesn't even talk to the children
I know how to do it. Because all the children's questions
There are similar ones. These people talk about their tad
They bring it very tight.
So she came to our house, sat down with my parents.
Talked a little, had some tea and pakodas. Then
He looked at me. in my eyes
Saw the questions and it turned on. saying
Say listen son, listen and see in life
Never keep your dreams small. you life
I can do whatever I want. do whatever you want
Take. People will say very negative things.
Don't listen to anyone because people already know
Not how big the scope of life is. You
To dream a dream and to fulfill it. Watching the next
To complete it. In the Process You Will See
How Much Life Can Expand How Many
Directions. She Like Trust Me Were You
Start from should never define where you are
And up just have faith all you dream
You can do whatever you want, whatever you want
Do it all, and in the middle of it,
If you get time, get married.
Do that and settle it once and for all, i.e. with someone
Do it, it doesn't matter, just do it
Hey, but why?
saying son
But look son, women who don't marry
Nor does she go mad alone.
exuse me? [laughter] Can you go crazy?
mental?
This is another problem in my family.
that if you tell someone that you care about them
If you don't understand something in the matter then
He thought the problem was only with the language.
Might be possible.
The matter may also be nonsense. This doubt is for anyone
Doesn't know at all.
And she's saying crack crack [crying sound]
[applause] [cheering voice]
Like you have [laughs].
All I'm telling you is here even at the 16th
Was not like this, there is no logical sense in this
It's not true, I don't want to believe it, but because
teaches us so much that from guests
You don't have to be rude and this
Particular woman was a little goddess in my
I turned my eyes and said no, no argument at all.
No, I didn't argue at all, but when he
I am sitting there finally gone from our house
My Entire Belief System Has Crashed OK
Yes, in a way, I don't like this.
The feeling came because I am realizing age
Children and teenagers consider us new.
Not there. We don't understand that our elder brother
People also get flooded. one of the same person
One opinion seems right and the other wrong. Age a
Child I Was Like How Is It Possible That
If 99% of what this woman says is completely holy to me
It seems to be the truth. So this is one thing that is so wrong
How can it happen? Either this is all true
Or is she saying all this wrong? and that made me
Very confused, very angry. I Felt
So bitrate. I'll tell you is the kind of
A feeling that many of us experience these days.
Is. When we did Kabhi Kabhie Na Kangana's interview
Let's see.
How did this happen?
Where did you go?
You were ours, right?
We are unable to solve this puzzle. Ok?
So I am 16 years old. I am sitting okay
With this confusing feeling. ok and i
I'm feeling very angry, okay, I don't know this.
Where should I take my emotions? I
I looked at my mom and said, you know what?
You can't be rude to guests but you can be rude to them.
So we can do it, what else can we do?
If it happens brother then I am saying mummy mummy
I said, Mummy, how can you say this aunty?
How did she go away saying that she
Women who don't marry are crazy to be alone.
Mummy goes and says, first we should do this
Don't talk, I'm saying okay, are I saying something?
Are we saying something? We never said anything like that
We are not saying anything, but this is what we see.
Has come.
Look, I do go a little crazy. And
Then mom started giving real life examples.
Look, that Sonia aunty of yours is yes
He never married. Now sit all day long
I keep straightening my slippers at home.
[Laughter]
Ok. Look at that Dolly Didi. Daughter in law
She keeps climbing the mountains alone.
I said that's called solo travel.
Buddy. Mummy says you can name it whatever you want.
Normal people don't do all that.
What I am telling you is that again at that
At the age of 16, I was not interested in any of this.
There is no logical sense at all. I absolutely
I will not agree. I logically and cerebrally
The matter was completely rejected. But Now When
I look back. Ok. Yes, in therapy. I
Realize that may be because I was really an
Impressionable age. And may be because this woman
Was a Literal Goddess in My Eyes. This talk
Go inside and sit somewhere in my subspace
Went. And I know this because this
For about 10 years after the incident, I
Never even thought about it. Ok. I
Think your late 18, early 20. So much happening
There is time. You move forward in life
yes. But I knew when I entered my late 20s
And That Is When I Feel Many of Us for the
First time get this idea of ​​agency that
Now I have repaid my debt to the world.
Now I have given everything to everyone
Is. Now I have done engineering, MBA, two years
I have done everything, job, depression for two years. Now
If I want to live my life the way I want to
What should I do? Ok? what kind of
Work Wood I Want to Do? where would i
Want to live? What kind of people do I live among?
Would I like to? What type of friends will I have?
Do I really want a partner? Do I Really
Want a partner? The answer came from within me.
Of Course You Want a Partner. A little crazy alone
It should not happen.
It Came So Smoothly and Swiftly From
I'm afraid. I was convinced of my own
Original intuitive is a wondrous idea.
I was convinced. No world fools me
She is not making it. This is my DNA, my higher
My self is guiding me that brother, someone
Only then will you go crazy. No, right? Yes. Any
You need a person to complete you.
And I was I was so convinced and I
Tried really hard. Ok? Some of this point
After 10 years, life has given me as much
You have always given me pleasure in life, whether it was
One task was not completed. need to find someone
Otherwise I will go crazy. And I I
Tried really hard. Ok? I tried really
Hard. Ok? I tried to be in
Relationships. I tried to date people. I
Fell in love so many times. I fight a lot
Mari brother. I vent on dating apps. I Made
A lot of people. Basically Over the Years I Met
Man after man and then I was like O I
will have to choose crazy okay I like o my
God
Mya I will have to suck crazy
I said if prevention is done through these people
If it is going to happen then I will embrace the disease
I would like to put
I [applaud] [cheering voice]
I would like to surrender to the disease. at least
In that case you will slowly go crazy. Yes. Slough
Gradual decay will happen.
All these bastards that I am meeting. Yes
Leaving after causing instant irreversible damage
Are. And you don't even say sorry once
Have been.
This is the point in the show. When I'm in the show
The men who have come [laughter]
I look at their faces once and a little
I see a bit of a relationship at work.
Look, let me tell you two or three things first.
Should I say that yes, you people have given the money?
He won't get it back okay first of
Secondly, no, I must tell you that, of course.
This is not about you guys, okay, not about you.
Guys this is not about all men nothing is
Ever About All Man Know
O no no no no [Appreciation]
Yes, those people who are spoiling our minds.
They are appearing from somewhere else.
Somewhere else among you people, he
There are no people, brother.
But more factually I also don't speak for
All women right? I don't speak for all
Women I speak for many. Ok? [Laughter]
Many are sitting here today. A but I must
also tell you that you know to the man in the
The Audience That Actually We're Living Through
Times where suddenly it has become so
Fashionable to hate on man inside ok hum log
Actually, I have been angry for a long time, but now I
People are getting a chance to remove some
Tell me, are people getting their money too?
So [praise]
It's a bit unfortunate for you guys, okay?
Yes, but let me tell you, this is the only
Only this side, there is another side to it that
As women, you should know that no matter how much we
Crypt, complain, rand
Take Against You Guys, About You Guys. The
Truth is as women. We will never be yours
He has a contribution in our lives.
Can't discredit. Ok? Absolutely
Can't do it. You Know Women Have Said Women
Have great creative energy inside them. But
A male force to activate it
Seems like And no, no, it's not about the bio.
I am doing it. Ok.
You Can Look at Anything in the World and See
It. Ok. You Look at Any Great Creative
Work by a woman? Great Poetry, Great
Literature, great art. To make all this
First one that seems to be a nervous breakdown.
So [praise]
No one can induce better than a man.
Can. Brother, write scriptures with your tears.
And the women.
Give it all to you. If you get this flu flop,
I am not interested in poetry art. look
At Women in Tech, Women in STEM, Writing
It's God. The most angry looking ass-kissing
I will give it to the world. I keep everyone awake
I will give. Where is the anger coming from? you only
People are watching and leaving. All are strong
Women keep saying Across the World. I
I am a phoenix rising from my
Ashes. Where is Ash coming from? where are you coming from
Is? Someone is going to make it, isn't he? automatic
It is getting a little better. All thanks to you people
Yes brother. [Laughter]
But the most honest thing I can say is
This is that I also know that this is inside me
The anger, the bitterness, the bitterness
Yes, it also is a function of age. because
I know that in my younger years, in my
Fertile Years I Have Also Been a Very
Big fan of the male kind. Ok? means a lot
Fan is a very small word to describe me.
To do. I am a bit of a devotional type
I have been. Yes, I was a little bit in priest mode.
I am. I have been pathetic. Ok? and which
Whatever level of pathetic you're imagining,
I have been more pathetic than that.
I have been very pathetic. because one is
It happens to be blinded by love,
Being romantically blind. I am non-romantic
I have already shown you how to remain blind. Ok? Mi
I've been that kind of blind
That you know when I just started working
Had done. Ok? And in a work space I would
C that brother, all the men in the cabin are wearing suits
How are these people sitting? I don't have this
Something felt very wrong. I said, okay friend
Maybe in a way they would have been a little superior
We are from the people. I say friend, among these people
Where are we, the qualities that humans possess?
Where do we have the qualities that we are 6
hourly work has been spread out to 16 hours
I don't have any attachment to my wife or child in my heart.
Spend 16 hours playing video games in the office
Where are we, people, that quality is within us?
Where
[Appreciation]
Man, there is so much diplomacy in these people.
That brother is chasing the boss like that
If you are in front, you will become a spoon, yes where?
Are we able to do it or how much can these people do it?
How much do these people know, how many people
No, never, I don't say no. Sometimes
I don't say no. Ask anything complete
An essay will vomit. take it from somewhere
I will come brother. So when all these soft skills
If there is no age woman in us then how can
We can compete with them. Give
Deserve to rule the world. I have been there
[ __ ]. Ok? And sometimes now when I look
Back at that version of me. Ok? and sometimes
When I Meet Young Girls Who Are Like This
Version of me. So I have a little brain too
I am shocked that brother how can it be that when
The Universe offers us so much as we
Women, we are so fixated on this one thing.
How do you do it and I have only one
There is a logical and scientific explanation that
God's hand is in this, see yes it is
[laughs] The Creators Conspiracy Okay there.
There is no other explanation, see the creator
Whatever name you give to him, he is the creator of the universe.
What is the agenda of God the Creator over us?
There is only one agenda for us that we
It is a species, it keeps propagating, okay, and
The Creator is a process set off centuries ago
He is doing it and is just chilling. Yes. Autopilot
But we keep propagating it.
Are. In our country it is absolutely amazing
They keep propagating it. We people
Have become exporters of species. Balance
People in the country are saying, brother, how much will you send?
You guys please take it back. every nook and corner
It is being sold. Tell me.
So it's been great. Creator. Over the centuries
He is chilling. We are leaving. But
I feel last few 50-60 years no
The maker has become a little angry.
Yes, the maker's stress increased significantly.
Is. Because in the last 50-60 years women
Suddenly I got too much freedom. suddenly
Women are like that wow me in this birth
I have got so much freedom that my mother and grandmother
Grandma was no less than anyone else. So this one
What should I not do in life? So many people
I should not live without a backlog. We have this one life
I have to do everything. Ok? us career
Also have to be made. We also want to see the world.
We have to study philosophy. We also get drunk
Is. We have to do everything. Everything has to be done. Ok?
Yes. We should not take leaps but jumps in our life.
We have to take it and evolve it. We all learn
Have to take it. Our entire social media
Content is also coming in the form of knowledge. yes that
Apply retinol and eat protein also.
Take quantum leave brother. You all manifest
Do it. We are here. Ok? We are the people of life
Got ready to take a big bite. We people
They are jumping around.
I am going to make a vile. to men too
Is watching. People are saying brother
What's up guys?
What is making these people so fuss? Man
People's social media content, dogs'
Meme.
Cat meme.
[Appreciation]
Dog and cat riding a bicycle together
People are saying everything is going well
Yes, what can we humans improve?
How much are you evolving in this one life?
Come on friend, in this one life we ​​have our
Learn to put your plates in the sink.
[Appreciation]
If you understand people's emotions then
When will you play video games?
The work to which I have incarnated. This
has a role in the world.
Which which is fair for you guys. You your
I am here right now on the journey. Ok? Butt you
Think about it, okay. Maker's Stress This Move
I am thinking that if it continues like this then how will
This leaping being? Ok? [Laughter]
Get attracted to this?
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
There was a fight too.
How will this Ganga flow like this?
[Laughter]
So the obvious logical explanation is that
that for some 15 20 years of our female
Lifes. Ok? in this age bracket of 20 to
35 God, come and enlighten our wisdom
Gives.
[Laughter]
Sorry, I'm putting it on low power mode.
You flow a little
[laughter] Go get the deed done my lord. Oh bad
So this is not it?
Some man came and said, I am tying my shoelace
I tie it to myself. You say oh my
God. [screaming]
O!
[Appreciation]
Did you make a video of this?
I want to say okay, I feel this is not really the
Biggest tragedy of the sequence of
Events. I feel the biggest tragedy and this
sequence of events just like that maker
In Order to Be Fair to Us Woman Kind.
Ok? That's by the time you hit your mid-30s.
He also comes and turns your intelligence back on.
So one day you get like what is this?
[Laughter]
When did I catch this?
[Appreciation]
I got a lehenga stitched for this.
Do not show the photo.
I'm telling [laughs] you this happens to
100% of us ok
But I feel the difference is okay that some of you
sitting here okay some of you sitting here who
I actually found love in this window.
Cultivate Relationships Who Build Families
Feel the tenderness in your heart saves your
Sanity is basically when your sanity comes back.
Also, you like it, you know what this diamond is.
No, it's a lump of coal
But it is mine, hmm, I will take it.
What do you want to do? You have to sit all day
Have to play video games. we we play play.
[Laughter]
Is this playing with a Batman T-shirt?
Is.
You come walking.
I [laughs] am telling you. It is annoying but
Keeps you saying. What I'm Trying To
Say is that the rest of us who slip through the
Cracks We Become Kangana Ok Is What
is what I am slowly
Slowly Arriving at
I understand that in your heart
If there is no love, there is only anger inside you.
There is hatred all the time brother.
I understood why my aunty was so
It flies brother, do it with anyone, it comes
Understand it now ok I understand ok
There is ample scope for going crazy, but the butt
The Great Thing Okay The Great Thing About
Living in a city like Mumbai in today
Time is that I am not alone in this okay I
Have a lot of friends who also opted out
for the same lifestyle ok who are
unpartnered single unmarried so I them too
I went and asked if you guys are feeling it too.
what that [laughter]
You are going a little crazy.
People are saying yes somewhere.
But there is no need to shout so loudly.
no today.
whichch whichch [nasal sound]
Makes Sense Guys. Ok. See already na age
Brand Management of Unmarried Women Hum Log
Our PR is going very bad.
People are already bringing binoculars to see that
Hey, what a cat has come to their house. saw
I brought the fourth
Brother, it's time to change the neighborhood.
Is.
And the ironic part is there are unmarried
Women Our Tribe Cannot Grow Through
Reproduction. Right? Yes, it can only grow.
Through recruitment. Right? So we are too like
I am having a lot of fun. Sister Come Here It Is
amazing.
[Laughter]
But I must inform you that it is always
Comforting to Have a Tried Right It
Comfort it's all comforting that brother if all
People are going crazy together in groups, yes.
So what a shame these four people are sitting here
Give it to me [laughs]
We're Going Crazy Together
Now Is Like Having Any Other Lifestyle
Issue that brother got arthritis as if
It's happening, it's happening, what can we do?
With age, they will go mad and go away
Today I can just drink water and come at the right time.
What can be done? I Have Actually Become
Very comfortable with this idea that Bhai Kabhi
Sometimes you have to go crazy. in fact I have
become so comfortable with this idea that
Sometimes when I sit at home and socialize
I pass time by scrolling through media.
and I see one of these
Posted by one of my single friends. The
Kind of post which was something like o
My God I am so happy to be single.
I carried the love of the universe within me
I just poured it out.
Now I enjoy life so much. This much
I travel. drink so much matcha latte
Am. I also make this much latte. hanging upside down
I live here.
I'm like she's gone completely crazy.
Full form has been attended here. this is a
Cry for Hebes SOS. Come on girls.
I have become very comfortable. Ok.
In fact, at the end of the 10th session, I
I'm telling my therapist the same thing.
Thank you ok great analysis quite a lot
I understood but
[nasal sound] I am
Realizing that whatever lifestyle choice is okay
Being partnered and single makes me
I am not feeling any particular pain, I am
comfortable with it so I am saying the question
For you then, this thing that's going on
I have it inside me [laughs]
Where are you coming from, at this point?
10th session my therapist telling me that you
No what many times you know someone's grief
Best to Overcome or Solve
This is not the way that we investigate
What is the source of it? It Might Be More
Fruitful to Look at What Is Your Reaction
To it. I said ya ya that but first you
Admit Defeat. Ok.
I said brother, how is this possible? go away
I am going through the bad street. Guys if this one hour
I may not be able to make you laugh at all at the end.
And then I say that you have explored crying.
Yes
You will get a feeling that some slippers
I might take it out and kill it. You will do it I
I will understand. I will empathize and understand.
Ok. So my What The [ __ ] Are You Saying?
Again Unfortunately Therapist Making
Sense. Okay, Ah told me how she was
playing to make how a lot of times a
whatever you are complaining about this
Restlessness. this pain is actually not
Coming from the Grief. it is coming from
Our need to suppress the grief. to control the
Grief to Overpower It. saying at first
You have to understand that whichever person you are
The grief you're dealing with is useless.
No, it is not. Say Abstract Grief It Already
Have a purpose in your life. She is saying because
You have this grief. one inside you
Restlessness is what you try to
Get New Things in Your Life to Achieve New
Things in Your Life to Know to Fill This
Void. Because of this, there is a possibility in your life
There is momentum, there is growth. Your Life Keeps
Moving Forward. secondly because you have this
Grief. U R N N N N N N N
An empathetic person. You connect better with
People who are sad, okay? who need
Understanding. She Like Now With This
Understanding If You Can Just Step Back
And let this grief be you will see that time
With this grief, it automatically takes its form
She will change, she will shrink, it will become
Something Manageable It Will Become Something You
Can intelligently interact with Kah Rhi Aap
Don't think of it as your vanilla
Personality Pe Chocolate Sauce Type Hai
exactness
[Laughter]
I said we are here to say everything
How do you come
How come Constant doesn't go away from my life?
Brother, the one who is insulting.
But I must tell you this conversation was
Definitely very useful. Because I think I
also understand now that we are all
Operating Through Times Where We Do Everything
Don't move ahead with some functional grief.
Have been. Your life could be perfect in others
People's Lives. Ok? but you could be caring
The Grief of Their Life. You chose not to have.
And it is perfectly okay. Because we have
There are so many tools to manage all this.
To do. We have therapy. we have
Meditation. Journaling from People to You
Needed Journaling helps you lose your crazy self
First it becomes visible to itself.
What is it
What has come out of me? oh my
God ok
Very entertaining. ok but but my favorite
The Thing to Do to Marry My Mental Health Is
I like listening to podcasts. Or
Typically, there are two types of podcasts.
There are. One is that interview format
One. Ah, in which typically someone very
Accomplished man interviews a loser
It has been happening. [Laughter]
I think that's also for your mental health.
They are good. Because because typically
You listen to that like oh my god these two
How can a man say such nonsense publicly?
And left.
At least that came to my mind, I said.
No. Well done, well done.
Good job. Train practiced. Ok. Good for
Ego kicks. Ok. But the Kind of Podcast
I'm most hooked to are more of these
Monologues. Okay the kind that claims that if
If you listen to this podcast, we will
By communicating directly with the subconscious
Will rewire you from within. I said
Wow man, correct the message by entering my ear.
I will give you mine. what a promise okay and
also because i have to take you know so many
Flights for this profession. it is so
Convenient. Downloaded before every flight
One Podcast. I start listening to it.
By the time I land. I am a different
Person only. Ok? It is amazing. I will
Give you examples. Like one day I
I listened to podcasts on the flight.
started a podcast saying how you
Become so magnetic from within that everything
I am drawn towards you I like wow land
I will become a magnet as soon as I do it
Brother, please prepare the plane's system.
Same Trip Return Flight Second
I'm listening to a podcast saying how you
Be so detached from within
That you rise above everything. I said
Then what am I doing on the internet?
In life?
Only this kinetic energy can be converted into potential energy.
Have I come to convert you? [Laughter]
[Appreciation]
But but I'm still very hooked to it. Most
Recently you know I was taking a flight
From Mumbai to Delhi. OK in Delhi
I had work. I live in Mumbai. This Was
also this very weird time when she was indigo
The flight had defaulted. Many more
Flights were running late. So I was already
Got a lot of stress. twice my
The flight got cancelled. then a third or another
I took a flight and that too was delayed by an hour. finally
After all the chaos, I settled into my flight.
Flight to Coff. I started listening to podcasts
Did. The topic of this podcast was How To
Embrace and Invoke Your Inner Divine
Feminine. Ok? Whenever I say this
I'm here to put a familiarity on women's faces
I see the look of. Yes, and men's faces.
I will look at the question again. ok in this one
Don't look at your mistake. Yes, this is a little
Heavy sounding you know concept is divine
Feminine and here ladies know that's why
No, I have come after reading some books. Theirs too
Coming to the reel wheel itself. Yes, someone
People have not come after doing any research. Yes, theirs too
It's just coming in their face like this. You
People are not able to come in people's reels.
Here the hot waves are not giving way.
Are.
The Ganges of knowledge is coming, so Sharma is back.
She should go back. So I will explain
It's my responsibility. of C podcasts
The topic was Divine Feminine. But its base
The concept was actually very simple. Which
Is something all of us already sort of no.
which is how the idea is of
Masculinity Being a Very Male Thing and
Femininity being a very female thing. This is what we have
outdated we know that this spectrum is and we
Everyone is somewhere on the spectrum.
in fact both this is masculine and feminine
Energetic Qualities Are Inside All of Us and
Who You Choose to Be in the World Is Where You Are
Find alignment. In fact, I have seen this many times.
Because all of it is inside us
You have different experiences in different environments.
Personality triggers. It's Seen Very
Offen Women. But you are very masculine at work.
She behaves. You are very feminine at home.
They live. Or it could be the other way around
You used to sit very shyly at work.
Are. Yes, not even a leaf moves and
As soon as he comes home he immediately picks up the whip.
Whatever the environment is being provided to you.
[laughter] So this is the rough base concept. Now
the podcast I'm listening to, the flight
Taking the level, saying in my ear that
women like you women like you
You people have come out of your homes like cages
Breaking the cage, yes, we are free from this life
If you run in the race, you will come first.
We will beat everyone and the people will be beaten.
I will remove the cucumber only
He's saying you guys have been cut off [laughter].
He is saying that you people have been cut too much.
You guys are running the race in the wrong direction. podcast
He is saying who gave you this wisdom that
Anyone would have benefited from participating in this race.
Is. Just take a step back and see how you can see this race.
Look at. Poor people have been thinking this for centuries
Running the race. Are running away. Then
Round and round they are running. Are running away. End
I'm having some heart attack. roll down
Have been. Yes, no one is getting anything.
is in this race. breaking the cycle which
Humanity has to come out. You armor
Wearing the earrings, he himself entered inside it.
You got a way out. Ok. you so
Got a free pass. You just need to know about your foams.
Go. I have to do it too. I have to do it too.
Ok? Just to prove the point, he got caught
has entered this race. And now yourself
You have overinvested so much. in
Trying to Win the Life of a Sad Man. That
You
Whatever natural gifts you possessed within you
As a woman, I have discarded all that.
podcast saying as a woman universe
gave you so much wisdom. Ok? So much
Cosmic wisdom gave you the whole world
Can dance on your fingers. You can't believe those fingers
I keep breaking the keyboard.
What a waste.
What a [ __ ] waste. God gave you a laugh
Gave the move of. You are trying to become a crow
Are. what a waste what a [ __ ] waste
And in this confusion, you are still here, right?
It is left over there. You could not become a man.
Someone has become like a monkey and is left in the middle.
In. No one is respecting you like this.
No one is respecting me.
In the Middle of the Flight. I am having a
Mental breakdown.
Now look, I did everything wrong brother. Yes all
It is being done to me. That's why I am sad.
My life is over over over. Suddenly Podcast
He says it is not too late yet.
I said how does he know my age?
I have not entered anywhere.
The broadcast is saying it's still not too late. You
You have come to the right place. next half hour
In I, we communicate with your subconscious.
do. The good news is that the one inside you
The feminine has not gone away anywhere.
[Laughter]
She has just sat on the side of the route. are saying
Yes, you must know that these are feminine people.
Let's do this.
These people sit on the side of the road. Then
They give vibes with money and so on. then speaks
No, what's the problem? Then you have to guess
Is. Hello baby what happened?
Yes. This is Batman's problem with his T-shirt.
Are you feeling it?
The podcast is saying don't worry.
In the next half an hour we will tell you about the angry woman hidden inside you.
Will communicate to the feminine that hello
Madam, what happened? And do it all once
After Once the Feminine Inside You Comes Back
And Tax Control Again, Tax Charge
Again, you will be back in your Goddess energy.
You will be in your Divine Feminine, your
Only the third eye will open. and saying that
As soon as this happens you will have to
Whatever feels wrong inside
All that will be corrected. which is in your heart
Whatever sorrow, pain or regret, let it all melt away.
Will go. Your gait will change. your hair
Will be happy. Your skin will glow. you will
Feel different in your body. You will find
Alignment. And most importantly, you
Will Find a Sense of Belonging That You Be
Missing in this world. Like, wow! I so
I haven't even subscribed yet. Wow!
Guys by the time I landed in New Delhi
T3 Airport I Was Divine Feminine OK I
I could not understand what has changed in me
Okay, but I could feel something has happened inside.
A little bit of my personality problem too
It is that no one should talk to me for a while.
So it's my responsibility to buy like me.
Okay, something must have happened, something must have happened.
I picked up my luggage from the top and boarded the plane.
I finally deboarded at the airport
Started walking. And this is when I
New Something Has Shifted Dramatically.
Because firstly you should know that you know I am
Wired in a way that I'm always too early
I live here only. Whether to talk or
I have to walk. Land at any airport, anywhere
I have a reflex that brother
Run out of here in three or four minutes.
pass in. No one would be waiting for me.
Is? But I'm Just Always Running at Any
Airports Across the World. Ok? I take no
Time. I am just running. Ok? But this day,
I start walking at this airport
Terminal. I'm like hey what happened
Is? How did my life change on its own? These
I have come to the set of Heera Mandi. What
Is it going on? What the Work is Happening?
Whenever I become I'm feeling no rush, no
Urgency. I am feeling so relaxed.
Ok? I'm actually feeling so centered,
So Present and You Must Understand Again
This is the time when this airline has
Defaulted. Ok? Airport Pe More Than
The usual chaos is going on. Ok? everybody here
I am having a chill drink. Typically when I see
Crowds like this I became an ash white
Person. Okay oh my god not my scene. Ok
But this day [laughs].
This Day I See This Crowd in Front of My
There. I'm like wow
Humanity.
[Laughter]
Ok. I don't know what hypnosis was.
Me. I find everyone's faces beautiful
Are. Everyone's voice is sounding sweet. Ok. I
I'm like wow! It's such a blessing to me among
The People OK OK Joe Four Minutes at the Airport
I can go out for a long time. I can do something.
I will walk around for 15 minutes and then I will leave.
I'm walking, I can feel people turning around
You are looking at me, I said wow man, how much
My other brother has changed my life, I have taken a bath in the morning.
I didn't even know
It's been 15-20 minutes, I just enjoy it.
airport and finally as I look at the
Me outside the airport exit
And the crowd and chaos are visible and I am feeling
Excited. I like wow ocean of
Humanity. Ok. Now this drop goes to Saigar
I am going to get water. OK [laughs]
I'm like wow I can't believe this is how
Other People Feel OK Is This What You Feel
When you have a sense of belonging. Ok
And I am walking towards this. Ok
Exactly I think wow man. I Can't Believe
That a podcast corrected my life
Gave. A podcast just flipped my mind.
Did it. it is it is so amazing to be
This person. I like why the [ __ ] was I so
Obsessed in Trying to Really Win a
My life it is so beautiful to be a
Woman? Ok? It is so beautiful to be a
Woman? I am feeling so good. Ok? I
Feeling so good? Why did I why did I
I rejected the woman inside me that
why was so obsessed with this idea that
The life of men becomes better. Absolutely
It wouldn't have been better. Ok. My Life Is So Much
Good? Everyone should be a woman.
It's so much fun to be a woman. Why? Why
Was I a student? Why did I think that
Being a woman is weak. Why did you think that being a woman
Is that why? Why? Why?
[Appreciation]
I took four steps to the airport. Hansi
Of humanity was absorbed. one minute
I found it very correct. I said, wow! This
Is What Belonging Feels Like Amazing.
The next minute a heart twitch came from somewhere.
He cut it and went away.
Someone from Somewhere Came Pitch by Bottom [ __ ]
Of Guys Divine and Feminine Both Left Me
Very hard, very hard, I was absolutely
Masculine in microseconds my brain
I was so angry suddenly now
The face looks like the next one. Yes, every sound in my ears
It is stinging. grabbing the whole world
I feel like killing. I was so angry
Okay, and in that anger, bearly I had
No curiosity that pinches me
Who has cut it? Ok. I really felt
Like, my cosmic hand has come from somewhere
To burst the balloon. Ok? it felt
like someone is trying to have a good laugh at
My Expenses. I was so angry. I tell
You and I were angry because little I was
Flying to Delhi to participate in an in
A Round Table of Empowered Women. Ok?
Yes. Now in the evening, no matter how much I
I should become important. Full Time Twitch Is Cut
Now. Yes, Twitch Now Not Getting Uncut.
Ok. [Laughter]
And as I am trying to get out of this
Crowd. OK, try to hold your pillar.
I have been. I am also that thing I am I am
Angry Because I'm Not Young Anymore. when
I used to be young I know that I used to
Find Ways to Tell Myself You Know What?
If something like this happens that maybe when I am a little
When I grow up I will find I learn more about
I will avoid all these things from the world.
can I do it or maybe I will earn enough
Resources and Respect in the World
It won't happen to me. Now I am old enough.
Ok. I am 38 now you should know this. Ok?
Or
It has been an hour since we started talking.
I'm 38 now yeah deal with it I'm 38 now
The Truth About 38 Is It I Know That I
There's nothing else in the world to learn or do
Nothing more I can do which will
Prevent this from happening if it happens today
This has always been there, it will always be there with everyone
You are reaching anything, anywhere in life
Jae It Only Takes One Hand To Come And Show
You Your Place in the World and That Is So
Sad that made me so angry I like me
I'm having some anger attack type thing when I
There was a couple standing near me like this
Went. He had no child in his hands. Children
How did you see your side Welcome? I
Said
And you must know this action only children
Was not shocked. Shocked me too.
Oh what the [ __ ] just happened. Ok. hey me
Something very major attack type is happening.
I panicked and threw both my bags on the ground.
Keep it. I held my head. I said [ __ ]
Man. What the [ __ ] has happened to me. And I
Sweat God. In that moment in my eyes
A cab passed by like this. LEDs above the cab
Kangana's face was drawn on the screen.
You're saying it like I understand now.
sister? or are there any other questions left?
Is. Yes, I won't let you go without driving you crazy.
These people will take you from here.
Guys before I and this [laughs] show.
I must tell you like this is the point. Me
The actual message to be given in the show is this much
It is there. Ok? That's all there is to it. but then you know
Whenever I do the show I feel like you know
There Some Young People in the Audience. and them
How can I let it go on such a cynical note? Edge
An artist is my responsibility that
If I have caused a problem, then something
Should I give you some actionable material? and the good
Thing About Living Okay, Almost Four
Decades of Life on This Earth. almost four
Decades. Almost, okay? its just bad
These things don't happen, right? good things too
It happens with you. So I want to tell you
That I think one phase of my life when
I Felt That I Was in the Presence of You
No Strong Divine Feminine Energy Was
When I was very small and I had to spend
Time with my elder aunt. actually me
It seems that whatever I have in my life
The concepts of love, affection, and romance are
I either got it from Yash Chopra ji.
Or have you met this Tai ji? which is
Actually a bit counter intuitive. because
Typically in our homes, Tai ji has this
There is no role responsibility. They
Typically, the avatar of bullying mums
Let's take it. But this Tai ji actually
It was very different and very unique. ok she
Was really so full of love. ok sometimes them
Look, she might be hugging nine trees someday.
Sometimes his feet will start dancing in the rain.
Sometimes seeing butterflies in their eyes
The water will come. If I make a video of them
If she had brought it, you people would have thought that it was acid etc.
It has been done. Ok!
She was like this brother, she was like this, okay he was
Really very very full of love my mother used
To Hate Her OK
He has a lot of free time in life brother.
Don't they have some work left anyway?
Brother, who dances to the tune of a crow like this?
And the truth is Tai ji was free
Zindagi mein because you know her husband my
Uncle was a resourceful man. enough at home
Staff was there to help. children grow up
Had gone to hostel. So she had that luxury
Of time and she had no shame in enjoying it.
Now it's a matter of a summer vocation. My Mom
out of town for a two-week seminar
Had to go out. Mummy is telling you to give
Leave her at Taiji's house for a week.
Have been. Make their life hell if possible.
Give. Isn't it? If possible, in Ravana's Lanka
Set it on fire and come back. my blessing
Is with you. I was only eight years old.
I had no such plans. Any
There was no plan. In fact, in two weeks
These were very good weeks of my life. First
So I realized that you know in two weeks that
If your father is not paying the AC bill every day
If yes, then sleep very well at night in AC.
It comes.
And secondly of course ok tai ji also
Made sure that my every day is very good.
Ok? I have a lot of fun. he is with me
She also used to play. Sometimes I get help in small tasks
I will tell you to water the garden.
Please help me. Sometimes my hand was engaged in sewing and embroidery
Apply it. and through out this she would also
Give me nuggets of wisdom about life. So
Eyes to Feel Like You Know a Very Grown Up
Person like one day Tai ji in her kitchen
She was standing and making tea and I was just watching them.
I was sitting and watching. Tai ji makes tea.
Talk to me. Say, look, son, this is
Evening tea is a way for a person to satisfy himself.
There is a reward. When we've finished our day's work
After finishing, he gives himself a cup of tea.
So you're telling yourself, well done.
I lived this day well. And when we stand for ourselves
If you start doing something like this every day, then
Then we got praise from someone and from someone else
There is no need for applause. so be it
If possible, do something like this for yourself every day.
Needed Treat yourself to a cup of tea in the evening
Needed [Appreciation]
I was only eight years old.
I was like these big people, very strange
There is a strange problem. Brother
But I could sense something important.
It is well said. So I made a small
Opened the notebook and started making notes. I
Said we will revise it when we grow up. Ok?
I am making notes here. Tai ji is here
She is making tea. Suddenly V.C.'s kitchen
A monkey has come and sat on the window. Tai ji
saw the monkey. She looked at me and smiled.
She is saying we [laughs] the monkey has come.
It's time for his evening tea too.
will be. We [laughs]
I make tea and give it to him also.
I said
What nonsense is this going on brother?
Then you have to understand that the kind of
Because of the upbringing my mother gave me
If you ever came to my house in the evening
If you call me, put some poison in your tea.
You can expect it.
It will be a little light, no doubt okay and you
Looks like a tax paying citizen of the world
Are. Extra tea for Taiji the monkey
Are making. My mind just exploded.
Tai ji looked at me. Saw my confusion.
Should I smile or not? Look son, love me
A person should do the same. in your heart
There should be so much love that whoever stands on the way
If you meet him, keep sharing your love. sharing love
I should never be negligent. His
What to do, the universe will see for itself.
No, and how many opportunities do we get?
So wherever you get a chance, whenever you get a chance, like
meet. Just keep giving love. [Laughter]
I am still only eight years old, brother.
I said take this word love five times
So it sounds very clean. on OK
I recorded the notes. I said brother
All this is a matter for later. Ok. I
Made notes here. Fresh instant extras
A set of tea cups was kept ready. to the monkey
Seeing this, the window started opening. So the window
The monkey ran away in fear due to the noise. Tai ji's
The shoulders sank. saying come in everyone
Time does not have the capacity to receive love
It would have been.
It doesn't mean that your love
Not love. I said, brother, algebra.
It is much easier.
Notes Notes completed.
Cut to another day, the exact same thing.
Repeats. Ok Tai ji is making tea here.
I am sitting and watching them. Monkey again
I came and sat down. Tai ji looked happy again. many times
Neither does love need words.
[sound of clearing throat]
[Laughter]
I said Urdu has arrived.
I did not understand anything about it but it became deep.
Clearly. Three times underline [laughs]
Tai ji again quickly made extra tea.
Made. Apna Bone China Six Cup Set
Removed. Tea for the monkey in a cup
Took it out. Open the window quietly and without making any noise.
And very slowly he slid the tea towards the monkey.
I Could See Monkey also has a second time.
Feeling a little confident. So he
Saw Tai ji, saw the tea. both hands
pulled the cup towards me, took a sip,
He threw it, then ran away. [Laughter]
Tai ji is again sad and saying come and give me love.
Time never gives me hope of getting my love back
Should not be applied.
I asked, what happened in his childhood, brother?
Someone please take out his slam book and read it to me.
Now, on the third day, I don't blame myself
Tai ji ok I think it's a human tendency
It happens that something that has happened twice is given
You start expecting a pattern then
On the third day, Taiji already had extra tea.
Having climbed up and prepared your set weight, the monkey of the cup
I am waiting for the monkey and now the monkey is not coming.
Two minutes passed, 5 minutes passed, 7 minutes passed.
The tea is getting dark here. Their
The mouth is getting disappointed here. Monkey Fire Somewhere
I am not giving. At some point Taiji
Finally gave up. Chaiwa closed her bow
Picked up the sieve from below. I turned around and saw the monkey coming.
Is. Tai ji danced like this. Oh my God. As such
His mouth burned like a halogen.
saw
If love is true, it will come back again and again.
It comes anyway.
I was like, this [ __ ] be crazy
Cap
[Appreciation]
Taiji quickly drank her black tea.
Taken out in a set of china. blow by blow
Of the cold. Who knows what the poor monkey's face will be tomorrow?
It may have burnt. Yes, the tea won't spoil.
I can, brother.
window
Open the window and serve the monkey tea with your own hands.
Moved to the side. And now, in this moment, this
This is what I was telling you about. in this
Moment, I could see that Tai Ji exactly
What were you trying to show me? Because such
He extended his hand towards the monkey.
No, I could see that in that one gesture in
Something was communicated between the two.
The entire body language of the monkey
Suddenly it became very soft. His entire one
It was a combat-like stance, but it disappeared on its own.
It's like it happened. He saw the hesitation in their eyes.
Took a step back. Then took two steps forward.
Then I looked into his eyes again. your hand
Slowly moved towards the cup. Tilt your head
I did it and then slapped Tai ji.
very hard slap
He pulled Tai ji and hit her. Sea Guys The Moral
of the story
actually is
No matter how true your love is
Be Abundant If the Person in Front of You Is a Monkey
Or
[Appreciation]
about to make a fool of you
or [praise] but I must tell you that this thing
I did not make notes. Me too
She was clapping like a savage.
Guys let's not forget I was only at
Years old. This was the highest point of
My life and I wow oh my god. what are you looking at
My eyes took it. I'm on Cartoon Network
Where will he be able to show something like this? of my eye
Tai ji got slapped in front of me. What
Content Have I Quoted? I went and saw the world
Sang it all over the next day. I said Tai
penance
Mom is throwing a party next week.
Gave.
[Appreciation]
From that day onwards I was under Taiji's curse.
I am living.
All my life, only monkeys have had tea.
Keep feeding me, friend.
Thank you so much guys. You be amazing.
[Appreciation]
Thank you brother.
I am I am very happy. Thank you so much.
I put a lot of ask for a better proud for
This recording. I am so happy for this.
O Man [Appreciation]
What?